Guide to the George D. Vaill Slide Collection of Yale Buildings and Grounds
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
George D. Vaill slide collection of Yale buildings and grounds
1975-1975
RU 679
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.25
The materials consist of slides by George D. Vaill depicting Yale buildings and grounds.
Vaill, George D.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-A (YRG 46-A), Records and materials broadly documenting Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
Arranged by subject.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of slides by George D. Vaill depicting Yale buildings and grounds.
College buildings; Universities and colleges -- Landscape architecture; Slides (photographs); Vaill, George D.; Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Buildings
- Slides, Series I
  - Aerials, New Haven, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 4)
  - Aerials from buildings, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Region 2, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Region 3, undated (Box 1, Folder 7 - 8)
  - Region 4, undated (Box 1, Folder 9 - 10)
  - Region 5, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Region 5 - Morse and Stiles, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Region 6, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Region 7, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Region 8, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Region 10, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Region 11, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Region 12, undated (Box 1, Folder 18 - 19)
  - Region 13, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Region 14, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Region 15, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Region 16, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Region 17, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Region 18, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Region 19, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Region 20, undated (Box 1, Folder 27 - 28)
  - Region 21, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Region 22, undated (Box 1, Folder 30 - 31)
  - Hillhouse, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Banners, undated (Box 1, Folder 33 - 34)